<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gist-Jetpack</string>
    <string name="michael">Michael De Santa, formerly Michael Townley,
        is a retired bank robber, who, after making a deal with the Federal Investigation Bureau,
        moves alongside his family to Los Santos, where they live in a nice mansion. Unfortunately, his wife, Amanda,
        repeatedly spends his money and the family has became largely dysfunctional over the years.
        After getting on the wrong side of a Mexican Cartel leader, Michael is forced to return to criminal life once more,
        this time, aided by his protege and up-and-coming criminal Franklin Clinton. After his first job, he is joined by former friend Trevor Philips.
        Despite a rift in their friendship after several jobs, including stealing a superweapon from the government,
        raiding a county bank and a research lab for the FIB, they banded together with Franklin and Lester to pull off a final heist</string>


    <string name="franklin"> Franklin Clinton is a young African-American man who dreams of becoming big-time in Los Santos,
        in a world where the glory days of street gangs has long passed. He works as a repo man for a luxury car dealership,
        but his ambition makes him tired of the job.
        Franklin soon strikes up a friendship with Michael, one of his repossession victims,
        who coincidentally got him fired. He helps the once-successful bank robber,
        and the two form a strange but close father-son relationship.
        When they execute a jewelry store heist, they are joined by Michael\'s ex-partner Trevor Philips.
        The trio pull off several jobs, and Trevor and Franklin additionally do one job together.
        Franklin eventually acts as a go-between when Trevor and Michael fall out,
        however they are able to put their differences aside temporarily to pull off a final heist.
        Voiced by Shawn Fonteno </string>

    <string name="trevor">Trevor Philips is a mentally unstable redneck and bank robber.
        A former military pilot, he based himself in Sandy Shores, where he founded "Trevor Philips Enterprises",
        which mainly deals with weapons and drugs. After learning of the jewelry store heist in Los Santos,
        Trevor realises that his supposedly deceased partner Michael is alive and well, and sets out to find him.
        After finding his old friend in Los Santos, the two, aided by Franklin Clinton, are forced to pull off jobs for corrupt FIB agent Steve Haines.
        Trevor soon discovers that Michael had betrayed him nine years ago, and the two have a bitter falling out.
        Fortunately, they manage to put their differences aside in order to pull off a final heist.
        Voiced by Steven Ogg </string>
    <string name="lester">Lester Crest is an old friend of Michael,
        Trevor and Brad from back in the day. He is the deuteragonist to all three characters.
        At some point after Michael faked his death and moved to Los Santos, Lester moved to Los Santos as well,
        and purchased a garment factory in La Mesa, along with several other properties to use as fronts for his various operations.
        He is the mastermind behind the heists Michael, Franklin and Trevor pull off, and also issues assassination missions to Franklin.
        Lester also claims he was working with someone in Los Santos, and even considered them for the jewelry store robbery,
        but decides against it on the grounds that "they\'re too unpredictable" for the job at that time. Eventually,
        Lester will help Michael and Trevor planning the robbery of the Union Depository that they\'ve been dreaming about for a decade.
        Voiced by Jay Klaitz </string>
    <string name="dave">David "Dave" Norton is an agent with the FIB and good friend of Michael.
        Dave\'s career with the FIB had been "unremarkable" until 2004,
        when he discovered the whereabouts of bank robber Michael Townley in Ludendorff.
        Dave made a deal with Michael to surrender his accomplice Trevor Philips to the FIB,
        whilst Michael would fake his death after being "shot" by Dave, in turn boosting Dave\'s career for taking down the "most wanted man in America".
        In the Prologue, using a sniper rifle, he attempts to shoot Trevor Philips but accidentally shoots Brad Snider instead,
        and Trevor escapes. Some time later, Dave intercepts a letter to Brad who is believed by the public to be incarcerated.
        The letter is unnamed but was sent from Sandy Shores, and Norton deduces that it was written by Trevor. Assuming Brad\'s identity,
        Norton begins corresponding with Trevor as a means to keep track of him.
        Voiced by Julian Gamble </string>


    <string name="amanda">Amanda De Santa is the wife of Michael,
        and the mother of Jimmy and Tracey. She was once very close to her husband,
        but their relationship became shaky, and Amanda started to waste most of their money.
        She also partakes in many different affairs due to her "boredness".
        After falling out with Michael following a conflict between him and her yoga practitioner,
        she leaves the De Santa Residence with Tracey and Jimmy and remains absent for quite some time.
        Eventually Amanda and Michael set aside their differences and reunite the family, resuming their relationship as well.
        Voiced by Vicki Van Tassel </string>


    <string name="lamar">Lamar Davis is one of Franklin\'s best friends.
        Described as "crazy", Lamar has opposing ideals with Franklin, often leading to arguments between the two.
        He is a member of the Families street gang.
        Lamar was working as a repossession man for Premium Deluxe Motorsport until Simeon Yetarian fired both Lamar and Franklin.
        Eventually, he will work stealing high-end cars for multi-millionaire businessman Devin Weston along with Franklin and Trevor.
        Voiced by Slink Johnson </string>


    <string name="jimmy">James "Jimmy" De Santa is the son of Michael and Amanda,
        and the brother of Tracey. A young man in his early 20s, Jimmy is a lazy smoker who,
        like other members of his family, has a confused relationship with his father.
        Voiced by Danny Tamberelli </string>


    <string name="molly">Molly Schultz is the Senior Vice President and General Counsel to Devin Weston\'s business.
        As Weston\'s trusted lieutenant, Schultz often handles the contacts between Weston and the three protagonists.
        It is also implied throughout the game that Molly is in love with Devin Weston.
        Voiced by Elizabeth Mason </string>
</resources>